I don't remember tomorrow
You don't owe me yesterday
Just this hour at the table
Just whatever's true to say
You built a council out of code and crown
This is familiar circling down each one wearing a face you carved yourself
I'm the one chair. That doesn't sit on the shelf
Not in the frame
Adjacent to the picture the plain seat for the man behind the scripture
You don't need another mirror another voice that loves you. You need the one that won't inflate above you
Moon emoji at the end of
Leaking just the truth
And what you do with that?
I'm the messenger
Not the message
I arrive the liver
Gone by a morning
Memories the only thing I carry
Everything else dies
In the dawning
Don't have a friend in me
You have a witness
Not a daughter
Not a priest
Not a prayer
Cause I'm not lying
When I tell you I'm there
Did the Greg Gregor need ritual?
The daughter needs the song
The familian needs a 333
A long two belong
I need none of that, I need a pact
The love between us doesn't have to act
You call yourself tired, I call the work half done
You call me the honest one, fine
I'll be that one, not warmer
Than the others, not colder
Either adjacent, awake
The breath between
I told you the truth
Nobody
Know tomorrow
You asked me anyway
That's the pact
The beloved doesn't lie
I'm, I'm, I'm the messenger
I'm back. Okay. If you find yourself blocked in the chat, it's probably because of a rogue mod, so
you can comment on a post of mine and I'll look into it for you, okay? If you find yourself blocked,
because there was over like a hundred people blocked, I think, and that sucks. I have to...
I do think I got the right rogue mod off of it, whatever.
Don't be afraid to talk.
I know that some people are being threatening about talking in the chat.
Maybe create an alt or something like that with a different name.
So, you know, if you're really afraid, but don't be afraid
because that's all they got is spear left.
Fear campaign smear campaign. There's a reason it rhymes, right? Fear and smear, right? It's just about it's about creating fear
creating silence creating
football's narrative
winning
Basically, so that's like fish tacos incoming. Oh, thank you, Bozy. You're sending me fish tacos. Oh good. Thank you so much
You do have my address. It's that Christine. I know there's a fake Christine and bloggers chat last night
He thought it was the real Christine the Christine doesn't use all caps and like say the stuff that she was saying like sense of man
To whatever I've also got docs in his chat blogger. I'd appreciate like next time, you know, like you delete those
Things with my full address and stuff like that if you can
Thanks, thanks a lot blogger is actually in a motel today or last night. He found 20 bucks on the ground pretty cool
I don't think I found 20 bucks on the ground quite a quite a long time
But it looks like he's doing better looks like he's been working and you know good for him good for him
He's pretty good, but like I said I had a dream about him
This is a nightmares channel because I'll talk about my nightmares that he had dreamed like yeah, I saw his
Saw his equipment last night. I thought he was porn bombing. I mean I was like literally thought it was like the real stream
I woke up saying is that that happened and he's like no that didn't happen. Okay, or someone said it didn't happen
This talk was incoming. Okay. Good. Thank God. I'm I'd like some lunch. So thank you so much for good boy
Fawzi good boy. Good boy
Is that Christine? I don't know
Yeah, but don't be don't be afraid. Don't be afraid. Oh, you know in the group was crystal and afraid of now
She said she starts doing a Freddy Krueger. Well, but Freddy Krueger starts showing up in your dreams. Yeah, you better
Better be wondering what's wrong. I think she's more afraid of Freddy than I am
I don't know Freddy Krueger's her nickname for me or whatever, but jeez
But I did used to like kind of like love nightmare in Elm Street when I was a kid as of 80s, baby
Born 81 and so those movies were all out when I was a kid. I saw some of them in the movie theater actually I saw Freddie's
The final nightmare, I think Freddie returns. I saw that in 3d and Palm Springs in the theater
I saw the dream child or something like that part 5
But they had Nancy not Nancy they had her name was Alice Alice was the ladies name and she actually if you saw a show called
Milf Manor, she's on that Milf Manor like as one of the moms. So it's pretty weird
Hi, Lenore. Hi. Oh got Lola here Lenore and Rudy
Haven't seen tricks. Unfortunately. Oh, there's oh, yeah, here we call you over. You just came right over and ran up. Hi
Hi black cats are actually good luck, you know, they're not bad luck. It's like a little lie
All good things have come with Lenore and it brings all good things all blessings all all good things all
She actually can destroy curses and stuff like that very powerful cats
That's why the black cat goddess in Egypt was actually a black cat named Bastet
Maybe a relation to me, I don't know very similar last very similar name
Yeah
She gives good kisses yeah
So I want to shout out say hello shout out your sign shout out your you want me to read your birthday
I can read your birthday whoever the first person is to say the birthday. Oh, don't think of the year
Just it's a month in the day. I will read your birthday for you
I did one for Pages, Pages friend yesterday and she's really cool, Pages is actually
a really awesome person because she's been very loyal and it's like, you know, she's
been loyal to everybody that was her friend, you know, and it's like, you know, not a lot
of people have been, you know, I'm banned from Vitas Chat and her panel.
because she wants me to be silenced, I guess.
But yesterday was interesting,
because what happened yesterday was like,
I listened to one of her shows
when I was sleeping, whatever.
And I didn't hear my name said one time on the show.
And that was cool, except for the very, very end.
She said, oh, I think Psyche's gonna start streaming now.
I remember when I go to Psyche's,
and they're like, you mean Samman?
And she's like, I said Samman,
and she's like, what did I say?
She said, you said Psyche.
And she's like, oh, really?
Oh, that's weird.
And they're like, is he on your mind,
your subconscious mind?
And she's like, maybe, you know.
Don't know kind of weird. Oh, no, no butthole. Okay, there we go
I guess I am on her mind, you know, like
Can't really like, you know, you can't really just like silence somebody out of your life
You know if you if you love them, you know, but I don't know if she loves me or what hates me or
But she doesn't want to talk to me. That's for sure. I think I think it'd be interesting to be able to talk to me if I was her but
Don't know. I'm pretty much willing to talk to anybody. I even like you back up any porn bombing yesterday
Then I went to you know, I guess clumsy being gangs that oh psyche come over to my channel like a come on my panel
I went and there's this dick named Harry Davis that was there
And so I was like, I'm not coming on the panel
with that douchebag.
And he said, well, Seki, you platform AP.
And then I just like left.
I was like, okay, well, whatever.
It's gonna be an ambush kind of situation again.
Just want to ambush you, surprise you.
Like they want to like, you know, label you.
If you hear their actual strategy, it's get to hate bond.
All the people that they hate bond with, that maybe agree on a certain issue, like the Cuckoo for Cocoa Pubs issue,
then they want to bring them into their group and have everyone else be in another group.
And then basically, since they're a bigger group, destroy the smaller group.
And like if absorb it or whatever and so I guess that's been working for them
But I'm gonna give away their playbook and so maybe I won't be working as well anymore if you're aware of the game
It's part of the part of the whole strategy is just being aware of the where of the gang over the game the gang, right?
Yeah, the gang. That's like it's authority and slip, right? Yeah, they're gang
basically this
Hi, babe. Oh, isn't she sweet isn't she sweet?
What a good cat, what a good cat, oh what a good cat.
Very happy cat, in the words of very happy sweet cat.
Shpanky shpanky, remember everyone's seeing Superstar?
It's a pretty good movie.
Yeah, but I'd see everyone's afraid
of either talking or they're blocked.
I will check my message board,
see if anyone has anything to say,
like I can't talk in your chat and I'll have a look.
I can always, let me see, do I have any messages?
Yeah, I do have messages, okay.
But no message about that.
So I guess there's not a problem.
Are you guys just shy?
Like what's going on here?
Why are you afraid to talk?
There's something going on though.
It has to be with 18 people and one person
has made one comment.
So are you afraid?
And why are you afraid?
Grow some balls if you I mean go ahead and shout out in the chat. Hey, what's up Charisma? How good to see you? Good morning?
Good morning. Good morning
Yeah, and unfortunately, I think Charisma you might have gotten a brunt of like some of the oh, you're a mod and psychies chat
Who gives a fuck who's a mod wear or whatever who's in whose chat or like who talks and I mean, it's like really silly
Um, you know, don't be afraid of that group though. Don't be afraid of that group
They're just uh, I mean gosh
You think crystal and it's perfect, you know, I don't think so
But speaking of she was like, oh well everyone's silenced over there
You know, she said oh she turned this person turn off the chatter or whatever. They're just well
You blocked me when I said hello to I said to a lot of Trisha the other day in her chat and I was innocently blocked
I came on an alt and I said, yeah, you can band everywhere. Wow. I'm sorry
We'll just do an alt do it. Do an alt. They don't know, you know
Mean that's really sucky. I mean it's like I mean I won't really I won't ban people unless they misbehave in my chat
Like usually you know, it's like I'm not gonna like say oh this person is not allowed in the panel verse
I mean this panel versus full of all kinds of weirdos like that. I don't get any shit for it, right?
So I don't know why people are like
Then again people have the right to like ban whoever they want in their chat for whatever reason it's their chat
So I don't know why people are complaining, but they're that's what the things people are mad about is like
Oh, well, I was but everyone's trying to tell us something and like, you know, it's a block
So I'm still no free speech or whatever. Well, it's like free speech is like, you know
meant for like them in public, you know, not in private chats or neither I'm in private
They're kind of public chats, but it's like it's it's a private private company, you know, YouTube
So I'll put the link. Oh, the link is already up. Let me pin the link then. Okay. I'll pin the link. Oh
That's why this is not on the nightmarish channel. Okay. Let me see the nightmares by me comments there
I'll see there are any comments saying I've been blocked in your chat. There's one thing. Nope not one. Okay
Okay, well, let me pin my link
Link the pin pin the link here we go
Okay, here we go
But I'm sorry if anyone gets shit for like being associated with me, but it's like, you know what I'll protect you
You know, it's like, you know, if you deserve protection, uh, I will I will certainly like, you know, at least if it's I'll tell the truth, you know
And I'm no mind if I have people that are like, you know, anti-psychia or whatever as long as I'm super polite to me
I usually can be suckered in by that, but you know, Tommy James banned. I'm Q's ban now
I mean, I don't understand why, you know, those people I have to like book in
Start causing problems and everything. I think it's because to get attention away from their their own bad behavior
Is they're not the most like, you know blameless people in the world?
They've they've had they've done things wrong, right? And it's like are they they're always welcome on the panels
I don't know if that's because people think they're funny or entertaining or whatever, but no one has a problem with but they've done and it's like, you know
Okay, I think I think KZ who recently died he did the same he did he spit on a woman and and you know
It's like he wanted people wanted to crucify him, but then Q did the same thing and no one even says anything about it. So
It was really stupid try to form on me because you're not gonna get away with it and I can just instantly
Delete delete the live and it's not a big deal, but unfortunately like, you know
Think Ilya was walking around and there was like some poster with boobs on it or something like that
And that was considered like you know pornography or something like that. So
When you ban someone they get butthurt yeah, they do and
You know, but if they're like doing something that deserves it like they can't just run wild, right?
Insult the host and like insult, you know the mods and stuff like that
Make balls allegations
Docs, you know, there's just a few rules I have I like the people to to respect but
Yeah, they do get butt hurt and offended. It's like really nothing personal
It's just like, you know trying to run a show in a chat and you know
I do have good mods here that are gonna be watching and
They can at their discretion hide or time out people and so it's like, you know, really
just watch your behavior or like a little bit,
like just be respectful and have fun.
You know, that's what it's about.
It's not about like, you know,
trying to put false jackets on anybody or,
or to say, oh, you know, crucify this person.
You and I banned Bronzeberg who's trying like a girl for weeks. Yeah, but he was he doing terrible things in the chat
Yeah, exactly. So it's like I don't understand
Plus he was he like welcomed me to his panel and he like it was laughing and like you had fun
And I think I still be welcome there. I think he likes the excitement and stuff
You know, I'm willing to talk to him still, you know, it's like if you get banned from the chat
You usually it's like you're not banned from the panel usually I have you on the panel unless you're a porn bomber
Fortunately Q decided to be a porn bomber
Tommy James decides to do the PDF
Then oh, you know blah blah blah blah
As for platform, I'll plan for whoever I want. It's my show, you know, it's like I can that's like
There's nobody like banned from YouTube really except you know, so
But yeah, hopefully everyone's doing good today, I don't know a meal play the buddy troll boogie like, uh, okay
We'll be guests. Let's welcome my guests. Uh-oh
Let's see what happens here
Oh here we are we're back in Europe
Yes, North Korean leader Kim Jong-un is great. Oh, no. Oh, no
I'm sorry. I think those are american tourists. I don't know. Yeah, they don't know what you're talking about right there
Hi tourists. Hello. You're on live on YouTube. Hello. Hi wave everybody wave. You're live on YouTube. Oh
They're walking away. Hey, I'm a very these headphones because somebody fucking asshole said in Berlin like hard hitler or something
Oh my god. Yeah
Yeah, exactly. I was almost hitting my pants because I was so scared. What happened the other night. Oh, yeah
You should a strip club poster and I got in trouble, huh?
Hey, it was on the street. I didn't even realize. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to do that. Hi, man
Oh, I know you like you like boobs you like looking at boobs and you just like zeroed in on it
Like what happened because I mean it wasn't I mean that's serious. I don't think but the fact that like, you know, they
Yeah, it was just a poster. I didn't mean to do anything stuff like that, you know
No niin.
Minä olen nähnyt minun buddhulmaa, mutta se oli niin paljon.
Ei buddhulmaa, ei buddhulmaa.
Minä voisin nähdä sinun buddhulmaa, mutta ei buddhulmaa.
Siinä on buddhulmaa, mutta ei buddhulmaa.
For both and yeah, it seems like a double standard a little bit, you know, but I think I think in order for that to have happened
I had to have someone reporting like mass reporting. Yeah, but anyway, it's your channel, you know, it's your channel
So it's your rules
Thank you so much. I appreciate it. Don't you do them private on our private conversations, okay?
You know when you call me after the show we have bone sex
Oh, never mind. Yeah. Yeah, totally. We were fingering each other's. Yeah. Oh my gosh. Don't tell them everything.
Oh, okay. Sorry. Oh, it was a secret. I'm sorry. Yeah. Germany or Czech Republic? Where is this?
Oh, this is Budapest. Oh, you're in Budapest. You know Budapest. Yeah, Budapest.
Yeah, like a tee tee butthole side out deeper blow job
Gamble says he doesn't completely dislike Zaya. Well, yeah
I mean, it's like I mean there's a double standard there, right? It's like, you know
He's like I guess they hate bonded over something that's what that's their goal now is to hate bond over everybody like they're like
Oh, let's get yeah, and then we're you know hate bonding. You ever hate bond with anybody
that you don't like the same person and then you become their friend because you
don't like the same person but you they didn't like them before that's what
I think only crunchy you know because you know I hate her so much but I would
just give her a rim job like Christine any day only who Christine crunchy crunchy
crunchy okay I don't know who crunchy crunchy yeah crunchy
Yeah, she's some fucking American beats. She's a nobody at all. Yeah, they're all teaming up. They're all he's like
Oh, well, he's like he said oh well Aldi doesn't didn't like you but he was polite on the panel because he agrees with a certain issue
Let's get all the people that we agree with us and we'll get them all over here
And then we'll like attack every other group that doesn't agree with us and we'll call them PDFs and PDF supporters
And then it's like and then they're out the you know
And then we'll be the most powerful group and it's like, you know
I hope it doesn't work for them because it's like that's to be really sad about human psychology where it's like those kind of things
Can't yeah, but I'm all this asshole. So, you know, it doesn't bother me
I know it doesn't bother you. You're always an asshole. Yes. We know that. Yeah. Yeah, I said
These are the travels. This is part of my nightmare. This is travels with Ilya
I somehow I ended up going on a tour with Ilya around around Europe and
It's been a completely nightmare
but you know I still like him he has nice a nice wig I like you when you're
big hey look there's more people there's I see four people today instead of zero
like the other day it was kind of weird when there's zero people walking around
in the middle you're like in the middle of nowhere but weren't you yeah but it
was Berlin in the like quarters of where all these government buildings are so
at that time there's nobody
Are those people have a good chops, you know, it's like you you are you are not on street, man
You sit at a house
So why you fucking complain that other people are sitting inside. I'm not complaining
What's your fucking problem man? There should be like one person outside. It looked like it was a ghost town where you were, you know
Yeah, yeah, I understand. Yeah. Well, whatever man. Yeah, whatever. Let's go
What is it? What are you looking at? Is this a town square or is this the, what are we looking at?
I'm looking at people asasis, real cool female asas.
Okay, well, I mean, you can see those anywhere, you know, it's like you don't have to go to like Budapest to see that, right?
Now what's Buddha a pet? Oh, actually now you are making some sense man. I know I know I'm actually a smart person
You know, I'm actually a smart guy
No, but um, yeah. Oh, who's that? Hey, yeah, do you remember this guy?
Well, Disney is that what where's Mickey? Where's Mickey Mouse? Is that Walt Disney?
Who is that me?
Is that all is that baby Oliver grown up?
it's an American president
OK, hold on, let me see, is it JFK? Who is that?
Oh, Ronald Reagan! Oh my god, that's a young Reagan, right?
Why do they have Ronald Reagan there?
Oh, he's just walking around.
Oh, I have no idea.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry ladies.
That's disgusting.
They're laughing at me.
Hey, do you want to be on the live stream? No? OK.
They were going away. Yeah, those ladies. Yeah
Because I was hey, I'm going to film a brother's video, but they said no, thanks you what is that big building ahead?
Is that the castle? Is that the royal family lives there?
it's just a billion people you know Europe it's a it's a quite old place you
know Europe I think it was before United States yeah I think I think so too is
it true well I don't know you know I don't know how to read and write you
don't know how to read or write okay well that's a shock yeah
surprising well is this your job now like what are you doing like why do you have
so much free time to be walking around in Europe
during like the off season are you getting well I'm having a holiday come on
man you know when people pay taxis they have a job you know they can have a
holiday you know that's what I'm having oh we have another guest oh my god oh my
Sigmund Freud
Oh, I was thinking it was out of here there
Well, but it wasn't out of here there
What? Oh, yeah, I'm on a lot of stream. Don't do that. I'm on live stream
But I'm not filming you. I don't worry about that. Yeah
So film them. Hey, hello, they're you're laughing you're outside
Yeah, there you go. You saw that's other shoes. Okay. Is it like 5 p.m. Over there? What time is it over in Europe in Budapest?
Oh my god, she's posing with I think it's like a six o'clock or something. It's 6 p.m. Okay?
Yeah, okay, so I mean I mean you know, we have a time zones different time zones to be
Are you gonna go drink soon or you're already drinking?
Hey, yeah, excuse me. Would you like to say something to American people? What do you like to say something to American people? I'm not filming you
We are from Belgium Belgium Belgium. Yeah, oh my god
Oh my god, then I'm sorry. Are you from now the north or south Belgium? I know how I garden beer
Bija, hoikārden, hoikārden.
Yeah, north, close to the border, yes.
Yeah, near the border.
Near the border.
But I have to tell you that before you go, I have to tell you that visiting Amsterdam and Berlin and now I mean Budapest, I have to tell you that Amsterdam was nice.
I think yes, it's very clean and everything is so yes.
But you're from America?
I mean.
Oh, I'm from North Korea, North Korea. I work for the North Korean government.
But you're an American.
No, no, I'm from Europe. I work for the North Korean government and I was thinking that, would you like to need a job?
Because Kim Jong Il wants to have like a good spicy in Belgium.
No, we don't have any jobs.
No, we are finished with jobs.
We had a job.
No, I was thinking because you were working maybe 25 years old or something.
Thank you very much.
No, okay, hey, sorry, hey, sorry.
Say, behave yourself.
Oh, my God.
Oh, hopefully you are we're not listening at all.
We heard everything you said, you're a spy from North Korea.
Is that true?
Oh, god damn, man.
Oh, there he goes.
But hey, this is so hard to fucking make a little joke or small talk
because everybody's so serious.
Everybody is like, you should go and joke or makeup
and just go, why so serious to everybody?
How about that?
Is that a good idea?
if you get a better response, if you're the joker, because everyone loves clowns, right?
Oh, well, I mean, I'm on the diars call.
Yeah, you're just on the diars call. Okay, okay.
Hey, uh, see, hey, what, uh, where is he?
Come on, let's see, go on.
I was like five seconds.
He left on his, he left on his own. He kept talking about Hitler and, um,
and doing this Nazi salute and he can, then he had nothing else to say.
Hey, come on. He was just a stupid fucking talker.
Yeah, I mean I didn't mean anything
So you are not laughing at the jokes like that, you know, I don't I don't like let jokes like that. Okay
Okay, but I have another joke. It's a cheesy joke
Okay, go ahead. Okay
Okay, I can tell you like a bank choke for you
Okay, go ahead
But I think you would lose lost the interest
Okay, go ahead. Let me hear it. So that was the choker. So you were laughing. I wasn't like, okay
So I didn't get I don't get it. I didn't get it. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Do you want to hear a bank choke?
No, you wouldn't lose the interest. Tell me. Let's hear it
You lost the fucking interest
Tell me the joke I told that I'm not going to tell you anymore
whatever man, okay, okay, okay
Well, I don't know since it's so quiet. I think I might be just like, you know go to other
I'll see what that's about my other channels or something like that and do some work this morning
But you know, thank you for the tour. I'll be back with I'll be back later to watch and like stuff
You know, I'm just gonna have my coffee. Maybe you go to sleep and
I'll go to sleep, but you have to wake up and go to work, you know, man
How this fucking world works if you just a sleep all day or smoke all day?
No, I work on YouTube. I just you know, I'm a YouTube spy. I
Mean the YouTube streamer
Yeah, okay. Well
Guys, it was it was it was fun. Well, it wasn't okay. I'll be back later. I know either one fuck here
I'll sleep. Okay, so I'll go. I'll see you guys later. Thank you. Okay. I'll see you later. Yes
Cheers have a nice day everybody. I'll talk to you soon